Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5552
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Contains newspaper clippings, including an article by Bayard Rustin, a copy of the Constitution and By-Laws of the Railway Employes' Department, and 1968 Platform Proposals.
- Other Organizations. Miscellaneous Organization - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Celebration of Senator Margaret Chase Smith, RLEA sponsored trip to New York for the Congressional Secretaries' Club.
- Other Organizations. Young Men's Christian Association, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Other Organizations. Harvard - Trade Union Program, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Other Organizations. U.S. Committee for the United Nations and General UN, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Other Organizations. National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Other Organizations. Dual Organizations - "Paper" and "Rump", 1968 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Other Organizations. Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Other Organizations. Labor Newspaper, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Financial reports
- Other Organizations. Special Election Year Editions of Labor, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Other Organizations. National Transportation Week, May 12-18, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Other Organizations. National Association of Railroad Passengers, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Correspondence and broadsides protesting the closing of passenger routes as a result of the Penn Central merger.
- Other Organizations. Golden Spike Centennial Celebration Committee, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Other Organizations. The Southern Pacific and Railroad Passenger Service, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  A report by National Association of Railroad Passengers
- International Affairs. International Affairs - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Contains "The Miners' International Federation: An International Labor Study," by W. Willard Wirtz, U.S. Secretary of Labor
- International Affairs. Japanese Exchange Program, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- International Affairs. Swedish Railway Union, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs, Bureau of International Labor Affairs (ILAB), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs, Team Managers, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- International Affairs. International Labor Office (ILO), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- International Affairs. News from ILO, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  Swedish labor publication, in English
- International Affairs. Press Release, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- International Affairs. New Releases, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  International labor publications, in English
- International Affairs. Information Bulletin, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Dutch labor publication, in English
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Problems - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Contains newspaper clippings
- Commuter Problems. Questionnaire on Passenger Service, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Commuter Problems. Philadelphia Service Improvement Corporation, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  Philadelphia Tunnel and SEPTA service.
- Commuter Problems. New Haven Problem including New York Area (Long Island), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  Northeast Corridor and Long Island
- Commuter Problems. Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  Includes pamphlet on BART system
- Commuter Problems. Port Authority Trans Hudson (PATH), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  Urban Mass Transit Act of 1964
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies - Passenger Service - Southern Pac between California and Louisiana, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  Docket No. 34733. Contains newspaper clippings.
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Service Improvements - HUD - Mass Transit Grants, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  New York MTA and Port Authority
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement - Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority (MBTA), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement - Chicago Transit Authority (CTA), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Commuter Problems. Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Project, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Precursor to Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (SEPTA)
- Commuter Problems. Washington Metro Area Transit Authority, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Contains annual reports for the METRO System.,
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies of Passenger Service between San Francisco and Chicago, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  ICC Docket #34924
- RLEA. File Index (Legislation), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Legislation. File 2. Legislation - General, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Committee reports, drafts of bills, correspondence, Consent Calendars, and AFL-CIO reports on Johnson's legislative agenda.
- Legislation. File 1. Legislation - General [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9a)
- Legislation. File 1. Legislation - General [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9b)
- Legislation. Truth in Lending Bill, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Letter and replies re Truth in Lending sent to Congress on 2/28/68. Contains computer punch tape.
- Legislation. House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Letter of May 2 enclosing St. Louis Post Dispatch article to House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee. Contains computer punch tape.
- Legislation. Manpower Development and Training Act Amendments, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Legislation. Civil Rights - Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Contains Civil Rights Bill of 1968
- Legislation. Railway Labor Act, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Legislation. Interstate Commerce Act, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Legislation. Interstate Commerce Act. Replies on telegram re - S. 757, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Includes statement by Don Beattie, executive-secretary of RLEA, before the Senate, pamphlet "The Case of the Vanishing Passenger Train," drafts of bills, correspondence, and a Senate resolution about the discontinuance of passenger trains.
- Legislation. Passenger Train Services - Discontinuance [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 17a)
- Legislation. Passenger Train Services - Discontinuance [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 17b)
- Legislation. Pell Plan, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Legislation. Passenger Train Services. Before the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Testimony before the ICC in re passenger service discontinuance and report of ICC to Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee from June 25, 1968 on Intercity Rail Passenger Service.
- Legislation. Passenger Train Services. Replies from Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee members, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  In re book titled "To Hell in a Day Coach" by Peter Lyon. Contains computer punch tape.
- Legislation. High Speed Ground Transportation - Demonstration Project [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21a)
  Includes lobbying for Appropriations for this project, a brochure from the Illinois Central, and statements by Donald S. Beattie and industry experts before the Senate.
- Legislation. High Speed Ground Transportation - Demonstration Project [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21b)
- Legislation. Repeal of Section 13a of Interstate Commerce Act, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Includes text of amendment to this portion of the Interstate Commerce Act. Contains a newspaper clipping.
- Legislation. Report of Proceedings Hearing held Before Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23a)
- Legislation. Report of Proceedings Hearing held Before Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23b)
- Legislation. S. 2658 - Interstate System - Vehicles Limitations, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Raising the load limit trucks are allowed to carry on the Interstate Highway System.
- Legislation. Letters and Reply's, all member of House of Representatives in re RLEA Opposition to S. 2658, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Legislation. Social Security Act, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Legislation. Medical Benefits to Retired persons (Medicare) 130:6-1, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Legislation. Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act 130:4, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Legislation. Mail, Parcel Post and Express, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Legislation. Full Crew Laws, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Legislation. Railroad Unemployment Insurance Situation, General, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Legislation. Right-to-Work Laws (States), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Legislation. National Labor Relations Act (right-to-work 14(b), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Legislation. American Municipal Association, Mass Transit, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Transfer of control of urban mass transit systems to Secretary of Transportation so that it will have its own department.
- Legislation. Mass Transportation (Amendments to Legislation Passed 1964), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Legislation. Waterways, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Legislation. Anti-Labor Legislation, General, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Legislation. Labor-Management Reporting and Discovery Act, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- RLEA. File Guide, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Government. DOT, Prevention of Railway Grade Crossing Accidents, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Government. Railroad Safety Board, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Clipping from Time magazine article with picture of railroad crossing accident.
- Government. DOT and RLEA Joint Study Group on Advanced Coupling Concepts, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Government. Report Forms Accident Reports, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Government. Rules for Reporting Accidents, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions re Signal Systems, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Public Notice bulletins.
- Government. Accident Reports -DOT- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Contains NTSB accident reports and statistical charts on accidents.
- Government. Rules for Inspection and Repair of Power or Train Brakes, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Government. Labor Department, General, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Government. Department of Transportation, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Government. High Speed Ground Transportation, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  Includes rail passenger statistics for the Northeast Corridor and the third report on the High Speed Ground Transportation Act of 1965.
- Government. DOT Study on Rail Mergers, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  Contains a newspaper clipping and two copies of DOT study.
- Government. Executive Branch, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  In re appointments to Pan American Railway Congress.
- Government. House and Senate, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Government. State Department - General, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Government. State Department A.I.D., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Government. U.S. National Commission in the Pan American Railway Congress, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  Contains documents in Spanish, including the conference proceedings from Buenos Aires
- Government. Payroll Savings Division, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Government. Office of Emergency Planning, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Government. Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Government. National Defense Executive Reserves, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Government. Motor Carriers General, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Government. DOT, Transportation Association of America, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Government. Membership and Staff Appointments, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Government. National Transportation Safety Board, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  Includes accident reports and bulletins.
- Government. DOT, Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases. Approval of Changes in Signal Installation [folder 1 of 2], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 41a)
- Government. DOT, Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases. Approval of Changes in Signal Installation [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 41b)
- Government. Bureau of Locomotive Inspection General, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Government. DOT Task Force, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  Contains "Report of the Task Force on Railroad Safety."
- Government. DOT, ICC, Safety Dockets - General, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Government. DOT App. Of Safety Appliance Acts to Track Motor Cars No. 32248, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Standards - Wage Chronology #40 - Non-Operating Employes, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Standards, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Government. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  "Report of Basic Policy Matters Under Consideration by the Interstate Commerce Commission"
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Government. ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Government. ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Government. ICC M-300 Reports, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Government. Statistics 100-150 Operating Revenues and Expenses, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Government. Statistics 200 Operating Statistics of Large Steam Railways, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Government. Statistics 220 Revenue Traffic, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Government. Statistics 125 Selected Income and Balance Sheets, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Government. Statistics 300-350 Steam Railways - Class I Wages Monthly, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Government. Statistics 210 Train and Yard Service, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Government. Statistics 0-950 Revenues, Expenses and Stat. on Freight Forwarders, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Government. Statistics 2-650 Revenues and Traffic of Class A and B Water Carriers, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Government. ICC Accounting Rules, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Government. National Mediation Board - General, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Includes pamphlet "A Directory of Industry Wage Studies and Union Scale Studies, 1960-October 1968" and an annotated draft of the Department of Labor's Occupational Outlook Handbook."
- Government. National Mediation Board, Public Law Board Decision on Procedural Questions, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Amends. Re Individuals as Bargaining Agents, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - General, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Contains organization chart for NRAB.
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Second Division, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Third Division, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Fourth Division, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Membership, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  Report "Grain by rent-a-train, IFA territory to Gulf Ports."
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Application of Awards, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board,, Awards Adopting Gunther Decision, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Party Notices, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Contains news releases in re Neil P. Speirs's appointment to the Railroad Retirement Board by President Nixon.
- Government. Reports for RLEA Meeting from Railroad Retirement Board, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Administrative Practices and Procedures, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Benefits and Railroad Unemployment Insurance System, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etc., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Government. Administration of Medicare - Financial Intermediary, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Government. U.S. Information Agency, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Membership directory
- Government. President's Committee Physically Handicapped, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Includes pamphlets "Performance: The Story of the Handicapped," the Committee's annual report, and a certificate of membership for the RLEA.
- Government. President's Committee Equal Employment Opportunity, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Includes clippings file in re decisions regarding railroad carriers and unions.
- Government. Civil Rights Act (agenda Item 2:19) (Formerly 3.66) [folder 1 of 3], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9a)
  Includes AFL-CIO bulletin with news stories on the Civil Rights movements, filings before the Equal Employment Commission against carriers and unions, information on gender based discrimination, and conciliation agreements.
- Government. Civil Rights Act (agenda Item 2:19) (Formerly 3.66) [folder 2 of 3], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9b)
- Government. Civil Rights At (agenda Item 2:19) (Formerly 3.66) [folder 3 of 3], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9c)
- Government. White House Conference on Human Rights, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Contains pamphlet "To Continue Action for Human Rights," the report of the President's Commission for the Observance of Human Rights at the end of its one year appointment.
- Government. Federal Housing Administration- 221(d)(3) Plan, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Continued planning to build low-cost apartments for tax benefits.
- Judicial. Jacksonville Terminal, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  United States vs. Jacksonville Terminal Company for violations of the Civil Rights Act with regard to promotions and seniority. RLEA members organizations served interrogatories for records and information.
- RLEA. RLEA General, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Letter to former President Johnson about watching the Apollo 11 moon landing.
- RLEA. Constitution and By-Laws, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- RLEA. Officers and Members, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- RLEA. American Railway Supervisors Association, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers Associations, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Letter in re union's withdrawal from RLEA
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Correspondence, includes mediation agreement.
- RLEA. United Transportation Union (Formerly BLFE, BRT, ORCB and SUNA), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Correspondence and newsletters.
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Correspondence and minutes of meeting of the Ohio State Legislative Committee of BRAC.
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- RLEA. United Transportation Union, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  UTU press release re merger with 3 black and white photos of chief executives.
- RLEA. Labor Cooperative Publishing Society [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25a)
  Board of Directors meetings, financial reports, and By-Laws.
- RLEA. Labor Cooperative Publishing Society [folder 2 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25b)
- RLEA. Labor Cooperative Publishing Society [folder 3 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25c)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- RLEA. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Correspondence and withdrawal from RLEA
- RLEA. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- RLEA. Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- RLEA. Railway Employes' Department AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Correspondence. Includes report to AFL-CIO Congress.
- RLEA. Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- RLEA. Transportation Communications Employes Union, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- RLEA. Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- RLEA. Canadian Affairs, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- RLEA. RLEA Meetings - General, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Minutes of meetings
- RLEA. February Meeting, Miami, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Correspondence, planning documents, and bills.
- RLEA. Agendas, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  For monthly meetings.
- RLEA. Reports of Counsel, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Itemized list of cases.
- RLEA. Assessments, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- RLEA. Wages and Rules - General, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- RLEA. Norfolk and Western Railway's Thrift Plan for Non-Union Employes, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  Contains letter in re Southern Pacific's Thrift-Plan, which was based on Norfolk and Western's.
- RLEA. 1968 Wage Rules Movement, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Section 6 notices in re sick leave and hospitalization.
- RLEA. 1969 Wage Rules Movement (Box 11, Folder 22)
- RLEA. Health and Welfare, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  In re GA 23111, GA 23000. Travelers' Insurance and benefits
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Company, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Group policy information.
- RLEA. Railway Labor Building, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- RLEA. Safety Committee, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- RLEA. Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidation, Etc., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Report on western railroad mergers by the DOT.
- RLEA. Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads, Labor Management Relations Committee, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Contains correspondence in re member organizations leaving RLEA and in re gender based discrimination
- RLEA. Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity (AAR-RLEA), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Contains speeches by various law makers at the Equal Employment Opportunity Conference, and wire report on racial discrimination deemed an unfair labor practice by the Supreme Court.
- RLEA. Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- RLEA. Washington Job Protection Agreement Cases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Section 13 Reports in re Washington Job Agreement 1936 with regard to formation of the UTU
- RLEA. In-Plant Education Program for Cooperating Railroads and Brotherhoods, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Pilot program to provide continuing education to 2,000 railroads employees in the Chicago area.
- RLEA. Legislative Representatives, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  No records contained in folder at delivery
- RLEA. Passes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- RLEA. Prospective Employees, General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- RLEA. Department of Research and Education - Applications for Employment, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- RLEA. Internal Revenue Service Forms No. 990, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- RLEA. Travelers Insurance Co., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- RLEA. Postage Meter, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- RLEA. Addressograph- Multigraph Corporation, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- RLEA. Office Equipment - General, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)